<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>
Alien UFOs - Personal UFO or Alien Experiences or Dreams
</title>
<link>http://www.alien-ufos.com/</link>
<description>
Post your UFO or alien experiences or UFO and alien related dreams. This part of the forum is of a more subjective nature so keep that in mind when replying to threads. Famous stories and related cases may also be discussed.
</description>
<language>en</language>
<lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2014 06:24:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
<generator>vBulletin</generator>
<ttl>60</ttl>
<image>
<url>
http://www.alien-ufos.com/images/bluesaint/misc/rss.png
</url>
<title>
Alien UFOs - Personal UFO or Alien Experiences or Dreams
</title>
<link>http://www.alien-ufos.com/</link>
</image>
<item>
<title>I need help!</title>
<link>
http://www.alien-ufos.com/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/62531-i-need-help.html
</link>
<pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2014 13:53:44 GMT</pubDate>
<description>
Hi, can anyone tell me somthing about this sing? Attachment 18981 (http://www.alien-ufos.com/attachments/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/18981-i-need-help-untitleds.jpg) i know nothing...
</description>
<content>

<div>Hi,<br /> can anyone tell me somthing about this sing?<br /> <a href="http://www.alien-ufos.com/attachments/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/18981d1397397065-i-need-help-untitleds.jpg" title="Name: Untitleds.jpg
 Views: 19
 Size: 21.5 KB">Untitleds.jpg</a><br /> i know nothing about this sign...maybe some of you know<br /> P.S. I'M NEW TO THIS FORUM AND I'M SORRY IF THIS IS THE WRONG SECTION...AND SORRY IF MY ENGLISH IS BAD</div>
 
 
 <div style="padding:10px">
 
 
 
 
 
 
 <fieldset class="fieldset">
 <legend>Attached Images</legend>
 <ul>
 <li>
 <img class="inlineimg" src="http://www.alien-ufos.com/images/bluesaint/attach/jpg.gif" alt="File Type: jpg" />
 <a href="http://www.alien-ufos.com/attachments/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/18981d1397397065-i-need-help-untitleds.jpg">Untitleds.jpg</a> 
 (21.5 KB)
 </li>
 </ul>
 </fieldset>
 
 
 
 
 </div>

</content>
<category domain="http://www.alien-ufos.com/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/">Personal UFO or Alien Experiences or Dreams</category>
<dc:creator>Ken122</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">
http://www.alien-ufos.com/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/62531-i-need-help.html
</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Events of my childhood</title>
<link>
http://www.alien-ufos.com/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/62522-events-my-childhood.html
</link>
<pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2014 03:07:13 GMT</pubDate>
<description>
 
First off, let me say i joined here many years ago, created one thread about "god", and i disappeared. If anyone who replied to that thread it's...
 
</description>
<content>
 
<div>First off, let me say i joined here many years ago, created one thread about &quot;god&quot;, and i disappeared. If anyone who replied to that thread it's still around, i apologize for abandoning it, as i see it reached 6 pages. I was in a very dark part of my life, and in a bad spot. Never the less, i am a man of the motto, i have to see it to believe it. This goes for et, ufo, ghosts, god ect. Regarding the story I'm about to recant, a few instances really, it probably could've been posted in the paranormal section as well. <br />
 <br />
 I grew up in a middle class neighborhood, in suburban Pennsylvania. My best friend, who I'll call J was the same age as me, he has a sister about 2 years younger. Our favorite summertime haunt, was an empty lot we called, &quot;the dirt pile&quot;. The House he lived in shared a property line with this lot, and both were bordering a cornfield. We called it the dirt pile, because it was a relatively flat grade, but there was a big wide pile of dirt at the back. And behind that dirt was about twenty feet of trees and brush, before the cornfield. The pile of dirt was at least 15 feet tall, and in the summer tall weeds would grow outta the top, making it look taller yet. We played there daily, building jumps for our bikes, and hanging out in between the corn and the pile, it was a secluded spot. <br />
 <br />
 It was late summer, andI was a fearless 10 year old. We played all day, until the street lights came on. That night i got a call from J. He claimed to have seen, something weird looking walking around back there. He sounded nervous, and as we were taking, he was looking out his back door, he said he saw it again. I told him to check it out, he refused. So i told him to meet me on the corner, and i grabbed my flashlight. <br />
 <br />
 On the corner stood J, and his little sister. I asked him again what he saw, and the only definitive thing i could get outta him was, something was pacing back and forth. I proclaimed i wasn't afraid, and i started walking towards that mound of dirt. The weeds growing out the top, made it impossible to see anything behind out, especially in the dark. As we got to the base of it, i was feeling a little nervous, but the were right behind me walking single file. I climbed that pile of dirt, and set down my flashlight pointing towards the tall weeds, as i prepared to part them. I pulled them apart quickly, i startled something that turned to look, and the lights were shining directly into a frightening set of eyes. I stood there for a split second paralyzed in horror, no more than 5 feet away. My friend and his sister must of caught a glimpse, they ran screaming and i followed. The event is still vivid, and i can still see the glare of my flashlight in those eyes. I can't say for sure what it was, but I've seen deer, fox, bobcat, opossum, skunk, raccoons and more, and all of them run when confronted, this thing didn't back off an inch. I do know that someone died in that cornfield many years earlier, and this was confirmed by a high school teacher years later. However, after this incident i developed an intense irrational fear of the grey alien.<br />
 <br />
 Later that year i started &quot;sleepwalking&quot;. It's a very weird feeling, to wake up while standing. I also developed nosebleeds, and severe headaches. I convinced myself the only explanation was alien abduction. This went on for years, along with other odd occurrences, until the last incident when i was around 17. In my bedroom, i had a tall halogen light, the kind with a knob that determines brightness. At the time i also had an iguana, whose heat bulb had to be threaded in, in order to turn on. I woke up one morning, the iguanas light was screwed in and on, and the halogen light was on, and cranked up so far it was buzzing. This is strange, because i require absolute darkness for good sleep. I shrugged it off and headed to the kitchen for breakfast. In the kitchen, my mom asks me what i was doing last night. I said what do you mean? She said she heard voices in my, and me arguing with someone. I was dumbfounded, and creeped out. I guess it could have been a sleepwalking episode, but i just don't believe that.<br />
 <br />
 Over the years I've become much more skeptical, and take everything with a<br />
 grain of salt. I still have no idea what i saw that summer night in that empty lot, but i don't believe it was an animal. Regardless of whether or not my encounters were genuinely paranormal/extraterrestrial, it got me involved in reading and researching the subject.<br />
 <br />
 I don't expect everyone to believe me, just wanted to contribute some personal experiences.</div>
 
</content:encoded>
<category domain="http://www.alien-ufos.com/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/">Personal UFO or Alien Experiences or Dreams</category>
<dc:creator>Rob</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">
http://www.alien-ufos.com/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/62522-events-my-childhood.html
</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>In Need of Opinion</title>
<link>
http://www.alien-ufos.com/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/62504-need-opinion.html
</link>
<pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2014 08:45:16 GMT</pubDate>
<description>
I registered on this site over a year ago because I had something happen to me; I wanted to see if something similar happened to others or if I were...
</description>
<content>
 
<div>I registered on this site over a year ago because I had something happen to me; I wanted to see if something similar happened to others or if I were the only one, or if I were absolutely off. First off, I'm not necessarily a skeptic, I'm the sort of person believes anything is plausible as well as not, anyways...to the point. <br />
 I was living at my old house in Fresno at the time, beginning of 2012; it was night and I was wide awake, I had a cat and a small dog staying in my room with me and they were doing their thing when suddenly I felt like I had been heavily tranquilized or something and everything got really foggy, I could hear my dog kiki going off as well as my cat getting on the top of my desk, my attention was drawn to my closet which was directly in front of my feet, I was super slow and groggy but very aware of what I was seeing. First I saw feet coming from what looked like the ceiling in the closet and then legs and torso and so on and eventually a being, a female, she was very tall and i dont remember her features very well only small things that I was able to force my brain to remember, those features were lips, pale purple skin, dry looking skin, pretty missing some facial feature and hair. She spoke to me and told me it was fine and I replied that i knew I was fine and I had an overwhelming feeling like I missed her, she spoke to me about some things and said she wanted to explain everything and I was in what seemed like a ship or at least an image of a ship, she was wearing something different when showing me the ship and there were other beings there too, she explained things about the human race and other races... And showed me so much information as well as her ship location and told me i was her greatest achievement and said that they were always watching... I dont want to get into too much detail, i just need help. When it was all over my cat was hiding with my dog and my feet were pointing the complete opposite direction... I got up and everyone in the house was practically in a comatose state and not everyone in my family sleeps at night lol.</div>
 
</content:encoded>
<category domain="http://www.alien-ufos.com/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/">Personal UFO or Alien Experiences or Dreams</category>
<dc:creator>tofusquid</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">
http://www.alien-ufos.com/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/62504-need-opinion.html
</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Saw bright light going across the night sky</title>
<link>
http://www.alien-ufos.com/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/62498-saw-bright-light-going-across-night-sky.html
</link>
<pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2014 22:15:54 GMT</pubDate>
<description>
I have seen a few odd lights at night, but tonight I saw what I first thought was a very bright star, but not one that bright and in that position of...
</description>
<content>
 
<div>I have seen a few odd lights at night, but tonight I saw what I first thought was a very bright star, but not one that bright and in that position of the sky. Then I realised it was moving in a slow NE direction. I ran and got my camera, which is not the best for taking video. In fact its crap and not easy to get started. I do use the video on odd occasions, so not entirely sure of it. The video just shows a bright light going across the sky and me having terrible camera shake as you have try and handle a 300-70mm zoom lens and keep it steady! Well I didn't and its all over the place, but I did get it. But all you see is a light in the sky. I checked to see where the ISS was and it was at the southern part of the planet. There was nothing else it could be as all aircraft have flashing light and make a huge din. This was extremely quiet. Time I took the dog was 9pm and it was in the sky for a good 10mins. Sent the poor video to MUFON.</div>
 
</content:encoded>
<category domain="http://www.alien-ufos.com/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/">Personal UFO or Alien Experiences or Dreams</category>
<dc:creator>The Small Grey</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">
http://www.alien-ufos.com/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/62498-saw-bright-light-going-across-night-sky.html
</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Have I been probed?</title>
<link>
http://www.alien-ufos.com/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/62490-have-i-been-probed.html
</link>
<pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2014 16:03:43 GMT</pubDate>
<description>
 
This is a very embarrassing thing to ask and I feel slightly retarded for wondering this but please don't judge me for it because I need an honest...
 
</description>
<content>
 
<div>This is a very embarrassing thing to ask and I feel slightly retarded for wondering this but please don't judge me for it because I need an honest answer.<br />
 <br />
 I've been getting a strange feeling in my behind which feels like somebody has stuck something up there and I'm not really su
 
 
re how to explain why I feel this way.<br />
 <br />
 I have not made any assumptions as to whether or not I have been abducted by aliens and/or probed by aliens as I have not found any evidence so I have been keeping an open mind and I've avoided making judgements since I have no knowledge of such a thing. Also, I'm not sure if this is true or not, but from what I hear, after being abducted by aliens, they wipe your memory so that you will have no recollection of what happened to you (does anyone know if this is true?)<br />
 <br />
 Anyway, this feeling is not sore or painful but it does feel odd and somewhat uncomfortable.<br />
 <br />
 I know it sounds ridiculous, ladies and gentlemen but I'm not sure how else this can be rationalised.<br />
 <br />
 What do you think?</div>
 
</content:encoded>
<category domain="http://www.alien-ufos.com/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/">Personal UFO or Alien Experiences or Dreams</category>
<dc:creator>The Black Panther</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">
http://www.alien-ufos.com/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/62490-have-i-been-probed.html
</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Nice Alien with Red Coat/Asked about Greys</title>
<link>
http://www.alien-ufos.com/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/62455-nice-alien-red-coat-asked-about-greys.html
</link>
<pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2014 02:24:14 GMT</pubDate>
<description>
I fell asleep the other night and awoke in a dreamlike world, I was happy and felt good in this environment. We were walking in a cloudy like bright...
</description>
<content>
 
<div>I fell asleep the other night and awoke in a dreamlike world, I was happy and felt good in this environment. We were walking in a cloudy like bright area and I was talking to a ET with a large color and coat telling me about their position in the world and humanity. I could sense his good natur
 
 
e and truth. I asked about greys after talking and he gave me a look as if he was surprised, and described them as sort of worker ants in the universe.<br />
 <br />
 He told me a bit more about other races, and then I blacked out and it seemed I was being examined. I was scared and closed my eyes but it didn't hurt and was quick. I woke up and was in my bed. It could have been a dream, but I was curious what you guys had to say.</div>
 
</content:encoded>
<category domain="http://www.alien-ufos.com/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/">Personal UFO or Alien Experiences or Dreams</category>
<dc:creator>LoveAll</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">
http://www.alien-ufos.com/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/62455-nice-alien-red-coat-asked-about-greys.html
</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hidden Knowledge Revealed?</title>
<link>
http://www.alien-ufos.com/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/62450-hidden-knowledge-revealed.html
</link>
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 22:20:58 GMT</pubDate>
<description>
Everyone interested, This drawing I have attached shows an image that I was introduced to in a very long and strange dream. The teacher in my...
</description>
<content>
 
<div>Everyone interested,<br />
 <br />
 This drawing I have attached shows an image that I was introduced to in a very long and strange dream. The teacher in my dream tutored and asked many questions of a small group of people I was with, and we seemed to be learning about the history of mankind as
 
 
well as something on space travel. We were on some kind of structure out in space which seemed to be nothing more than a large floor. <br />
 <br />
 I drew this on computer shortly after awakening from my dream and think it is very close to what I saw. The teacher had asked me as well as others so
 
 
me questions for which I participated in--I also wrote this down with my response on the drawing. The bottom circle shows perhaps the craft but this was never specifically identified as to what it was--I just felt it was. The amount of distance was being discussed, and on how to perhaps cross this vast expanse of distance in space.<br />
 <br />
 This doesn't exactly provide any immediate new information on UFO's, but please share this with people that could extrapolate with perhaps more depth. Any other questions or comments are welcome as I am interested with this information. <br />
 <br />
 What I have here is all that I know from the image in my dream.<br />
 <br />
 <a href="http://www.alien-ufos.com/attachments/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/18873d1397081896-hidden-knowledge-revealed-dimensional-travel.jpg" title="Name: Dimensional Travel.jpg
 Views: 36
 Size: 42.0 KB">Dimensional Travel.jpg</a></div>
 
 
 <div style="padding:10px">
 
 
 
 
 
 
 <fieldset class="fieldset">
 <legend>Attached Images</legend>
 <ul>
 <li>
 <img class="inlineimg" src="http://www.alien-ufos.com/images/bluesaint/attach/jpg.gif" alt="File Type: jpg" />
 <a href="http://www.alien-ufos.com/attachments/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/18873d1397081896-hidden-knowledge-revealed-dimensional-travel.jpg">Dimensional Travel.jpg</a> 
 (42.0 KB)
 </li>
 </ul>
 </fieldset>
 
 
 
 
 </div>
 
</content:encoded>
<category domain="http://www.alien-ufos.com/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/">Personal UFO or Alien Experiences or Dreams</category>
<dc:creator>Dulguldor</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">
http://www.alien-ufos.com/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/62450-hidden-knowledge-revealed.html
</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Family member missing and suddenly reappears?</title>
<link>
http://www.alien-ufos.com/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/62433-family-member-missing-suddenly-reappears.html
</link>
<pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2014 19:47:45 GMT</pubDate>
<description>
 
I've been trying to research this since it happened about a month ago. I finally decided to ask about it even though I'm terrified of the answer,...
 
</description>
<content>
 
<div>I've been trying to research this since it happened about a month ago. I finally decided to ask about it even though I'm terrified of the answer, terrified it'll happen again, and terrified people will think we are crazy.<br />
 <br />
 My husband is a disabled Iraq veteran. He suffers from P
 
 
TSD and often stays up really late at night because he's paranoid. It's not uncommon for him to come to bed at 3-6 AM and sleep during the day. <br />
 <br />
 It was a Thursday night and we had gotten into an argument earlier in the day. He wanted to go somewhere with a friend and I didn't want
 
 
him to go and he was upset with me. I went to bed (as usual) around 11 PM and went right to sleep. We live in a small house and I keep the bedroom door open, so I can generally see the light from the TV in the living room on the walls of the bedroom.<br />
 <br />
 I woke up at 3:18 AM and it was very dark in the house. Our bed is pushed against a wall, so to get out of the bed, I either have to crawl to the end of it or go out on my husband's side. I sleep against the wall. I know that I crawled out of bed on my husband's side. (And there's absolutely no way I crawled out of bed without noticing him--he is a VERY large man--6'7&quot; and 275 lbs.)<br />
 <br />
 My first thought was that he waited until I was in bed to go with his friend. I grabbed my cell phone and the house phone and tried to call his phone and it went straight to voice mail. I noticed both doors were locked, the car/house keys were on the table like usual, and his shoes were still here. I was frantic because I was concerned he had some kind of PTSD episode and had wandered off or something. I went into the bathroom (right next to our bedroom) and frantically kept trying to call his cell phone and was crying very loudly, &quot;Where are you....where are you....&quot;<br />
 <br />
 Now he is a large man and our house is on pier-and-beams, so I can hear him walking around. He just suddenly appeared in the hallway saying, &quot;I'm here. What's wrong? I'm here.&quot; This was at about 3:41 AM. He was gone for at least 23 minutes.<br />
 <br />
 I hugged him for a few minutes and we both laid back down in bed. He said I cried the rest of the night (though I don't remember it).<br />
 <br />
 At the risk of sounding like a lunatic, I explained to him what happened later that day. He says he does not remember getting up out of the bed, only hearing me cry, and being in the hallway. He noticed there was a cut on the side of his hand and a few days later, he pulled a tiny glass-like object out of the cut. He never bled.<br />
 <br />
 Does this sound like an abduction? He has had a lot of weird experiences in his life, but I didn't know him yet. I have been scared to go to sleep since then.<br />
 <br />
 Thanks if you read through this.</div>
 
</content:encoded>
<category domain="http://www.alien-ufos.com/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/">Personal UFO or Alien Experiences or Dreams</category>
<dc:creator>kintun</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">
http://www.alien-ufos.com/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/62433-family-member-missing-suddenly-reappears.html
</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Abductee looking for answers.</title>
<link>
http://www.alien-ufos.com/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/62417-abductee-looking-answers.html
</link>
<pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2014 03:54:37 GMT</pubDate>
<description>
 
I'm a male of 43 years of age and I like to think of myself as a fairly rationalised individual. I rarely indulged myself in magical thinking as a...
 
</description>
<content>
 
<div>I'm a male of 43 years of age and I like to think of myself as a fairly rationalised individual. I rarely indulged myself in magical thinking as a child, I have been tested for psychosis and temporal lobe epilepsy and neither were present, I had no belief whatsoever in extraterrestrials and the
 
 
very idea of my abduction experiences being a substitute for a human abduction is just out of the question, and yet at 12 years of age I was abducted by a group of aliens who look entirely human in their appearance. These abductions continued throughout my teenage and adult life - I can clearly rem
 
 
ember well over 70 abductions and I have never been hynoptised - with my last memory of being abducted being around 5 years ago.<br /> <br /> I have no idea which group of aliens my abductors are as people seem to use different names for aliens that fit their description, but I'm guessing these will
 
 
be the aliens that people like to call the Nordics as they fit that description very well. Roughly 40% of them have blond hair, roughly another 40% have various shades of light brown/dark blonde hair, and the remainder have very dark, black hair. They are all caucasian in appearance, and they fit the European Azilian/Maglemosian racial mix to a tee (Ancient British, Germanic, etc). They fit this racial mix so well in fact, and possess all of the body language that us humans also possess, that I'm convinced that their ancestors were human and European, and that their ancestors were also abductees who were taken from our world many thousands of years ago and transplanted elsewhere by some other extraterrestrial species. With the exception of their telepathic ability, possible telekinesis, the limited emotional range that they display due to their people always brainwashing each other, and the strange way they scream when I have had the opportunity to spin their jaws with a sharp right hook, they do not seem to be anything other than human. I have accused them of being shape-shifters, but their reaction told me otherwise. <br /> <br /> I could go into more detail but what I really want to do is to find people who have been abducted by the same group of aliens, and compare their experiences with my own. I have carried out much research on the net concerning this particular group of aliens and all I ever read is positive stuff, and yet my own experiences with them have been anything other than positive. If any of you have ever been abducted by these specific aliens please do reply or get in touch privately - my questions will be probing, but I pass no judgement on your experiences should they differ from my own.<br /> <br /> <br /> I also have a few questions that I'm hoping abductees of all alien groups may be able to provides answers to:<br /> <br /> 1) Have you been abducted by more than one species of alien? If so, how do you think it is possible to experience the misfortune of being abducted by two different types of alien? <br /> 2) Have you ever witnessed other beings on the ship? Say robots, or other biological beings? What did they look like? Were you able to detect any character traits?<br /> 3) Ever seen non-abductee humans on the ship? Do you have any idea of who they were, or why they were there?<br /> 4) Can you describe the inside of the ship? Its estimated size, shape, colour, layout, etc?<br /> 5) Did the aliens wear any uniforms? If so, what did the uniforms look like? Any belts, buckles, buttons, zips, etc? What was the colour of the uniforms?<br /> 6) Have you ever eaten their food or seen them eat of drink? <br /> 7) Have you ever seen them exercise? How was it done? <br /> 8) What is the modus operandi of your stay on the ship? Is there a set routine or a common theme to your stay? <br /> 9) What do you think their primary purpose for abducting humans is? <br /> 10) Have you ever been put to work? If so, what type of work? <br /> 11) Have they ever used molecular manipulation to remove your body parts or use you as an anatomy model? <br /> 12) Have you ever encountered them down here on Earth? <br /> 13) Are your abductions teleportations are are you levitated up into the air? Have you experienced both?<br /> 14) Have you passed through windows or walls? If so did you feel as though the solid materials were being manipulated so that you may pass through them, or did you feel as though your body was being manipulated so that the solid materials passed through you?<br /> 15) Ever been pinched in the day time? Surrounded by people who didn't seem to notice you had been abducted? <br /> 16) Do you have any idea if the abductions will ever stop, or do you think they continue throughout life? Do you think there an age limit to the alien use of abductees, and if so why?<br /> 17) If you're a primary abductee do you have any idea how many other people have been abducted as a consequence of your abduction? Have you seen family and friends on the ship?</div>
 
</content:encoded>
<category domain="http://www.alien-ufos.com/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/">Personal UFO or Alien Experiences or Dreams</category>
<dc:creator>xero</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">
http://www.alien-ufos.com/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/62417-abductee-looking-answers.html
</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>My father came to me in a dream/experience</title>
<link>
http://www.alien-ufos.com/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/62408-my-father-came-me-dream-experience.html
</link>
<pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 19:09:14 GMT</pubDate>
<description>
 
This was today, probably 5-6 AM. I am asleep, deep asleep. The voice of my deceased father pops into my mind and he says: " I only have one hour to...
 
</description>
<content>
 
<div>This was today, probably 5-6 AM. I am asleep, deep asleep. The voice of my deceased father pops into my mind and he says: &quot; I only have one hour to talk with you&quot;. My fear is so great that I decide to terminate this experience/dream immediately. I don't know why I fear my deceased father, any deceased person in my dreams. Maybe because it is as recent as two years? Why do we fear the deceased ? Ghost stories WE heard when we were young?<br /> <br /> Tonight I will consciously ask for him to try again and for me to be able to engage in a conversation before I go to sleep. I am asking that at this very moment.</div>
 
</content:encoded>
<category domain="http://www.alien-ufos.com/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/">Personal UFO or Alien Experiences or Dreams</category>
<dc:creator>krytoniteforthesoul</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">
http://www.alien-ufos.com/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/62408-my-father-came-me-dream-experience.html
</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Where to begin..</title>
<link>
http://www.alien-ufos.com/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/62384-where-begin.html
</link>
<pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2014 22:34:56 GMT</pubDate>
<description>
 
(Please forgive the length of this post!) I've spent the last hour agonizing over where to begin. So much has happened to me that it's impossible...
 
</description>
<content>
 
<div>(Please forgive the length of this post!)<br /> <br /> I've spent the last hour agonizing over where to begin. So much has happened to me that it's impossible to pick a starting point and begin from there. In retrospect, I have come to terms that whatever this is has been in my life since chil
 
 
dhood. My parents would attribute my experiences to night terrors or something I had watched on TV. Basically, as a child - I was terrified to sleep at night. Looking back, I realize now that none of it was the manifestation of a health imagination. There are days when I wish it was.<br /> <br /> My
 
 
entire life has been riddled with unexplainable phenomenon. As I child, I would have a terrifying night friend I would call 'Boo'. He was accompanied by a group of similar looking 'things', but they were 4 to 5 feet tall, and I'd scream when they would appear. They appeared white, but their eyes we
 
 
re large and pitted. They would peer around my bedroom door or from my parents bedroom door from across the hall when they visited. 'Boo', as I called him, looked exactly like the smaller ones, but he was intimidatingly MUCH taller, and he would (at least to my recollection) walk through my bedroom
 
 
wall. I called him 'Boo' because of the noise he made. Thinking back, it wasn't so much a 'boo', but a noise that made a deep reverberation. My younger brother (who was quite little at the time), started to talk to me about his 'friend' that would walk through walls. I was terrified. He would sit in the living room and talk to the walls. It was so bad that it started to scare my mother. <br /> <br /> These things (or beings) visited for a very long time, but then they disappeared. As my brother and I grew up, we moved north to New Hampshire. We lived in a beautiful in the middle of nowhere. It was a quiet neighborhood with good families. I was about 12-13 years old when things began to happen again, but this time it involved my entire family. It started during the summer of 1985; I remember it well. We lived in a two-story house. At the top of the stores was a picture window that overlooked the driveway and the tree line. At night, you could see the stars.<br /> <br /> One morning, I woke up because I heard my mother at the top of the stairs. When I left my bed to see what she was doing, she turned to me and pointed out the window and said, &quot;Do you see that, hon'? Do you see it? I've been watching it every morning for a week.&quot; And yes, I saw it. It was an enormous flying disc that was flying silently over the trees. The morning sun glistened and shimmered off its side. My mother was unnerved and called my father over to the window before it disappeared. My father stared in disbelief too. <br /> <br /> As the days carried on, strange things started to happen, especially at night. My father was constantly waking to the sounds of banging - or what he called, 'the sounds of someone trying to break in'. He would step outside, search around and also check the driveway. We had a light for the driveway, and he would turn it on before going out there. But this isn't all that happened. The sounds of heavy construction could be heard in the woods behind our house at night, between the hours of 12am and 3am. Now, you'd think that maybe the town was working on something, but 1) the woods were uncultivated and 2) it bothered my parents so much, they finally went to Town Hall to find out if construction was actually occurring. They found out there wasn't. In fact, it bothered the authorities so much, they even sent the police to our residence to search the woods, but nothing was ever found.<br /> <br /> The saucer would continue to appear every morning at 5am like clock work. We didn't live anywhere near an airport and it didn't make a sound. This continued on for a while until one evening...<br /> <br /> We were all watching television in the living room together. I don't recall the exact time, but it was slightly before dusk. It was still bright outside, so visibility was very good. I remember walking up the stairs to my bedroom, but then suddenly felt compelled to stop at the window at the top of the staircase and stare outside. I tried like hell to fight the urge to stand there and stare out the window, but to no avail. Suddenly, a triangle-like object flew in from over the trees and rapidly approached the window where I stood. It's really HARD to describe. It was like dual triangles, but they were placed together at the base. It stood up vertically and it spun clockwise rapidly with a light in its center that trailed and pulsed. It was a pitch black metal that had a shiny finish. Deep line-like groves were all through the metal (if it was metal? I am describing it the best I can here). <br /> <br /> I yelled down to my father because I wanted him to see the object before it disappeared. He raced up the stairs and stood there next to me. The object was so close, we could have reached out and touched it if it weren't for the windowpane being there. Now, my family has discussed this before, and this is where everyone has different versions of what happened next. Based on what I recollect, I remember standing there next to my father in absolute amazement. But suddenly, I heard my brother laughing downstairs and my mother panicking. I saw my brother race to the kitchen screen door (the door could be seen from atop the stairs), and he pressed his face against the screen and said, &quot;What's that mama?&quot; My brother was about 7 years old at the time. He then said, &quot;I want to see what that is!&quot; I saw my mother run up to the kitchen door as my brother bolted outside. My mother chased after him, but it wasn't even seconds later that I heard my mother scream, &quot;Jesus Christ, what is that!&quot;<br /> <br /> That's when everything felt like it stopped. Next thing I know, I am standing beside my father at the window atop the stairs, and it's pitch black outside. I could still see that triangle object spinning at the window. Suddenly, it bottled off into the darkness. This is where it gets strange from my perspective. All I can remember my father saying was, &quot;Boy, that thing was wild looking.&quot;. I could only assume he meant that triangle object outside the window. Oddly enough, every one went about their normal business that night except me. I was the only one acting unnerved. My memories of the night were broken and disjointed, but at least I remembered something.<br /> <br /> It took me 30 some odd years to finally corner my brother about that day. While he claims he doesn't recall leaving the house, he does remember running upstairs and seeing me sitting at the edge of my parents' bed in a trance, staring at the wall. He also mentioned that my father was sitting on the opposite side of the bed in a trance as well, but he was staring outside the window. He says things get too foggy beyond that point to remember.<br /> <br /> This is just one of the MANY experiences from my life. And yes, this crap is still on-going.</div>
 
</content:encoded>
<category domain="http://www.alien-ufos.com/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/">Personal UFO or Alien Experiences or Dreams</category>
<dc:creator>StrangeDays</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">
http://www.alien-ufos.com/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/62384-where-begin.html
</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hello, I am StrangeDays</title>
<link>
http://www.alien-ufos.com/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/62381-hello-i-am-strangedays.html
</link>
<pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2014 21:08:47 GMT</pubDate>
<description>
Like many here, I stumbled across this site while looking for answers. Since childhood, I have been experiencing phenomena that I have tried...
</description>
<content>
 
<div>Like many here, I stumbled across this site while looking for answers. Since childhood, I have been experiencing phenomena that I have tried desperately to rationalize. My first experience occurred during the early 1980's and it involved my entire family. No matter how many times we discuss the
 
 
event, we all seem to have disjointed memories of what happened, where we were in the house, etc. This was just the beginning, though. I spent most of my life trying to pretend that my experiences were a manifestation of my imagination. It wasn't until I got married that I realized it was real; I had to accept it. My wife is an environmental scientist by trade and a natural born skeptic. It wasn't until she started to experience these events with me that I realized there was truth to any of it.<br /> <br /> I waited to post because I feared ridicule. I wanted to browse the posts here to get a feel for the community. I have been to other sites where users have mocked people for posting their experiences. From what I have read so far, I see that A LOT of people here have (and still are) experiencing the same things as us. When I do post my experiences (and there are many of them), I can tell that the community here will be objective with their answers and even chime in with their own experiences to validate mine. I never thought any of this stuff was real. But then again, what person would until it happens to them?</div>
 
</content:encoded>
<category domain="http://www.alien-ufos.com/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/">Personal UFO or Alien Experiences or Dreams</category>
<dc:creator>StrangeDays</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">
http://www.alien-ufos.com/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/62381-hello-i-am-strangedays.html
</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Alien Dilemma</title>
<link>
http://www.alien-ufos.com/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/62353-alien-dilemma.html
</link>
<pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2014 03:58:59 GMT</pubDate>
<description>
 
[Don't tell me this is in the wrong section until you read it... It has to do with personal issues that just happen to have been influenced by...
 
</description>
<content>
 
<div>[Don't tell me this is in the wrong section until you read it... It has to do with personal issues that just happen to have been influenced by extra-terrestrial experiences...]<br /> <br /> I have reasoned my experiences to be fake, and have reasoned the entire notion ridiculous...<br /> <br />
 
 
However, through several visions, dreams, and abductions I have found a calling to a field of science. [Note: Visions being the transportation of consciousness during regular activities during a regular day to a different 'dimension' in a sense; and dreams being dreams; and abductions being whateve
 
 
r in the hell they are]<br /> <br /> The alien creatures I had claimed to have heard and seen constantly told me, and tried so very hard to convince me, about this certain field of science, and I just found out what it is and how it works... They tried to teach me and convince me that it was something I 'didn't have a choice about', and that they would [after they left] 'come back and make sure that I was following them' and etcetera... all of the usual scheiße -- but I'll leave the rest to be implied...<br /> <br /> It turns out that my alleged 'destiny' was to work on magnetic propulsion -- involving Gravitoelectromagnetism [and such sciences]. Through this, I have found out how the 'craft' they wanted me to design may somehow end up working. Naturally, I am interested in this science, but having a drive of extra-terrestrial origin is providing to be a dilemma... A very young man getting direct instructions from an advanced alien race on how to build a revolutionary spacecraft just DOESN'T happen and ISN'T real, and I KNOW that...<br /> <br /> <font size="3"><b>1: Should I pursue my life long dreams, regardless of whether or not they were influenced by 'me' or not?<br /> 2: Should I abandon the venture, due to the bad origins of the strange obsession?<br /> 3: If 'they' are fake, then 'they' are truly 'me', and it was 'me' that influenced 'my' decision, so can it really be harmful to me?<br /> 4: Continuing 3, did my bias of my belief in their existence directly influence me to 'manufacture' these ideas in the first place?</b></font><br /> <br /> This is proving to be a very difficult decision, because soon in my life [sooner than I think] I will have to dedicate myself to a line of work, and that of which I am the most interested in has 'bad origins' in my life... Should I even trust them that their idea will work? Maybe they DO exist and they will come back and haunt me if I do not choose to do this? They TOLD me that they would not allow me to ignore it, but assuming they do not exist, I will see if I want to attempt to [ignore them]... 'They' [ultimately myself, implying that 'they' don't exist] engraved the images and the idea into my head, and I really feel that it may be wrongly influencing my future decisions... because it is what I feel to be my one true calling regardless of them; which is probably because I [most indubitably] AM 'them'...<br /> <br /> <b><font size="3">I would appreciate any insight... Thank you...</font></b></div>
 
</content:encoded>
<category domain="http://www.alien-ufos.com/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/">Personal UFO or Alien Experiences or Dreams</category>
<dc:creator>jerrylee22</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">
http://www.alien-ufos.com/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/62353-alien-dilemma.html
</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>an odd night</title>
<link>
http://www.alien-ufos.com/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/62351-odd-night.html
</link>
<pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2014 23:46:50 GMT</pubDate>
<description>
The experience i had was Wednesday night, it was 7:30pm abouts and my wife just got home. And halfway through eating chicken pot pies from kfc I had...
</description>
<content>
 
<div>The experience i had was Wednesday night, it was 7:30pm abouts and my wife just got home. And halfway through eating chicken pot pies from kfc I had this really odd sensation so i muted the TV,and there where no birds chirping at all and a strange vib that persisted,we both noticed it and sat t
 
 
here for a min or two in the dead silence,it was kinda creepy .About a hour later it was dark by this time i had ran to the store for some drinks and when i got back and was making my way to the porch when i heard some strange sounds coming from across the street behind the houses, there is a creek
 
 
that forms a marshy pond behind them just over a cliff thats 50ft down and on the opposite side of the pond there is train tracks that run through town along the creek. but anyway the sound i heard was like a squirrel barking running around barking but it was like it had to have been a freaking huge
 
 
damn one buy the sound of it, i also heard limbs snapping as it ran around making the noise,like something huge was mimicking one ,or it might have been some dang big bird like a hawk or owl maybe either getting attacked or attacking something.I`ve heard bigfoot around here before,howls and woodknocks so that made me think maybe a teen bigfoot acting up goofing off i dont know if its related to anything its just i never heard nothing like that down there. Anyway later that Wednesday night we were sleeping my wife and i and the two dogs, (and i have to say monday i had banged up 3 ribs hopefully just bruised and i have not been able to sleep on my left side since monday). A little after 3am thursday morning we all woke up exactly at the same time dogs too and i was on my left side,there was no way couldve went to sleep on my left side with out pain even laying on it is agony,and for all of us to wake up at the same time was weird. Then later at work theres a girl i work with that lives at the opposite end of the block along the creek. She said her pit bull was freaking out running the fence barking and would not shut up and she says she has never seen her dog act like that and was curious if i heard anything last night about 3 am. I told her about the sounds i heard but that was it not saying my thoughts on it.Anyway later that thursday night we find bruises on the both of us ,two on the inside of her left thigh,then one on the outside of my right elbow and one on the inside of my right thigh all looking like finger bruises.the last two years about this time of year i heard wood-knocks and a screaming howl like a bigfoot comin from the area i heard that strange sound last night.but last night i was convinced it was just a hawk or owl or something.but to wake up last night like we did with the odd vib earlier in the evening and the strange sounds all in the same night is weird and im assuming it was an abduction again ,the last encounter i had with a grey i suddenly woke up and instinctively looked over at my wife and the grey was on top of her and when he noticed i had woke up and seen him he vanished,ever since that time its been difficult to tell if they have been here or not mostly just something telling me so in my gut a hunch of sorts.all in all i think im going to do some adventuring in the creek and train tracks very soon looking for odd stuff that aint right.but im kinda leery of the pond cause ive had to kill a pigmy rattler some years ago that came from over there i guess.anyway i guess there back again, at least they could do is fix my dang ribs and maybe other problems i was born with while they have got me wherever,doing whatever.So there was an odd vib earlier that evening,strange sounds,everyone waking up at the same time and finding bruising the following day.And i keep feeling like theres a damn string hanging off my left arm shirt sleeve down around my elbow ever since for two days now,and its starting to annoy me,cause theres nothing there.</div>
 
</content:encoded>
<category domain="http://www.alien-ufos.com/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/">Personal UFO or Alien Experiences or Dreams</category>
<dc:creator>coubob</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">
http://www.alien-ufos.com/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/62351-odd-night.html
</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>My parents experience</title>
<link>
http://www.alien-ufos.com/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/62324-my-parents-experience.html
</link>
<pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2014 05:32:46 GMT</pubDate>
<description>
 
Hi everyone, This is an experience of which both my parents witnessed. I aren't sure of the exact date but it was in 2006 when we used to live...
 
</description>
<content>
 
<div>Hi everyone,<br />
 This is an experience of which both my parents witnessed. <br />
 <br />
 I aren't sure of the exact date but it was in 2006 when we used to live in a small village in England ( now live in brisbane Australia since 2007 ) <br />
 <br />
 It's quite hard to explain but basica
 
 
lly one night both my parents suddenly found themselves both sitting bolt upright at a 90degree angle with there backs against the head board in bed. The whole room was lit up by what they describe as the brightest and purist white light they've ever witnessed, there were no shadows and the light didn't hurt their eyes even though it was so so bright. Everything was eerily quite. They distinctly remember feeling confused and scared, they looked at each other and without actually saying a word they spoke to each other in there heads, asking if they were both seeing this, if they were ok and what's going on. <br />
 Both really confused they sat there for a while but don't know how long, after sometime, these are my dad's exact words he said &quot;I slithered out of bed terrified and crawled towards the window to look out&quot; but he could see nothing, he even carried on to go out side to look around but could see and hear nothing. <br />
 They really Arn't sure how long they sat there, how they got there (sitting upright in bed which they say they never did or do) or when or how the white light disappeared. They don't even remember going to bed that night. <br />
 <br />
 They never told me about this until 2008 sometime, but both are adamant that it happened and with (both) my parents telling me this I do believe them, if it was one of them it could be passed off as a dream but surely not with both. At first i was confused about this and didn't have an answer, it was just something weird that my parents told me then soon to me became forgotten. That is until (As stupid as it sounds) I watched the movie 'the forth kind&quot; and could see some resemblance that I did a bit of reading and research and have come to find that this is quite a common experience and am now a strong believer. I find this so interesting that not only both my parents but many people around the world have similar experiences. <br />
 After reading a few books of peoples &quot;experiences&quot; where they are hypnotised and recall the events of what happened to them I now strongly believe that my parents experience was the aftermath of an encounter with beings not of this earth. <br />
 <br />
 Thanks for reading.</div>
 
</content:encoded>
<category domain="http://www.alien-ufos.com/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/">Personal UFO or Alien Experiences or Dreams</category>
<dc:creator>1pom</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">
http://www.alien-ufos.com/personal-ufo-alien-experiences-dreams/62324-my-parents-experience.html
</guid>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>